

# DAVID FESTEN

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT, FULL STACK DEVELOPER

### **PERSONALIA**

ir. David Wilhelmus Jeroen Festen Rotterdam, Netherlands d.festen@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/dfesten 16-10-1989

#### GENERAL SKILLS

Dutch: Native
English: Fluent
Driver's License: Yes

#### TECH STACK

Likes working with: .net Framework/Core, NodeJS React, Angular, Typescript, GraphQL, Python

#### **PROFILE**

I am in the software industry since 2013, currently in the role of architect. I love solving problems pragmatically and I am a huge advocate of privacy and proper work ethics. My primary interest is in emerging technologies such as AI, Machine Learning and Big Data. I enjoy working in teams that adapt modern technologies such as NodeJS and GraphQL.

I work in the position of Software Architect at a large multinational via ALTEN. My team creates monitoring & control software for the oil industry.

As a freelance software developer, I work for a client on a custom ecommerce solution and inventory management system.

*Profile:* Ambitious, Innovative, Leadership and Adaptive. *Passions:* Traveling, music making, running, skiing, golfing and scuba diving.

#### RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

#### ALTEN (CLIENT IN OIL INDUSTRY) | 2020

- Instrumentation and control software
- Architectural role
- Working in a full-stack agile team

#### ALTEN (HORTICULTURAL CLIENT) | 2019

- Logistic software
- Full stack developer
- Commissioning the software on-site around the world

#### M&C PROTECT | 2013 - NOW

- Built a custom business to business e-commerce platform
- Incremental improvements of the platform
- Maintenance of the e-commerce platform

#### ACADEMIC PROGRAMMER | 2014 - 2015

 Worked on Genius; an Al platform for automated agent negotiations (ii.tudelft.nl/genius)

#### STICHTING HOMBURG BONDS | 2012 - 2013

- Built custom single-use software tool for supporting a live voting process over two countries
- Built single-use software using OCR for recognizing handwritten votes

#### EDUCATION

### Master of Science in applied computer science and artificial intelligence

Delft university of technology | 2013 - 2018

#### Minor in applied artificial intelligence

Delft university of technology | 2011-2012

#### Bachelor of science in applied computer science

Delft university of technology | 2008 - 2013

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

SURVEY ON EVOLUTION OF ANAC AGENTS' SEARCH STRATEGIES

DELFT UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY EDUCATIONAL REPOSITORY **2019** 

### **EVALUATING MULTIPARTY MULTILATERAL TURN-TAKING PEER NEGOTIATION PROTOCOLS**

DELFT UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY EDUCATIONAL REPOSITORY **2018** 

## ALTERNATING OFFERS PROTOCOL FOR MULTILATERAL NEGOTIATION

MODERN APPROACHES TO AGENT-BASED COMPLEX AUTOMATED NEGOTIATION **2017** 

#### A GREEDY COORDINATE DESCENT ALGORITHM FOR HIGH-DIMENSIONAL NONLINEAR NEGOTIATION

RECENT ADVANCES IN AGENT-BASED COMPLEX AUTOMATED NEGOTIATION

2016